[

](https://zeroeyes.com/)

a

    * [Our team, our mission, and how we can help prevent your people and property from mass shootings and gun violence.](https://zeroeyes.com/about-us/)
    * [ZeroEyes is making headlines. See what people are saying about our AI gun detection technology and the difference it’s making.](https://zeroeyes.com/press/)
    * [See our current partners, view different types of partnerships, and learn how to become a partner and join our mission to end mass shootings.](https://zeroeyes.com/partners-inquiry/)
    * [If you’re seeking purpose-driven work where you’ll make a difference every day, you might be a good fit for our team. Here’s how to apply.](https://zeroeyes.com/careers-portal/)
    * [We actively utilize the DoD-SkillBridge program for transitioning active-duty personnel to the civilian workforce. Find out more now.](https://zeroeyes.com/zeroeyes-skillbridge-program/)
    * [ZeroEyes’ proprietary gun detection technology is an added layer of security, but our human, U.S. military-trained monitoring is what sets us apart from others. Check out our ZeroEyes Operations Centers (ZOC), where we verify threats before triggering real-time alerts and safety protocols.](https://zeroeyes.com/zeroeyes-operations-center/)
    * [We partner with innovative leaders driven to help protect the schools, businesses and communities they serve. Get in touch with us here.](https://zeroeyes.com/contact-us/)

    * [Education, commercial, government, places of worship, non-profit…the list goes on. Learn more about the industries we proudly serve and protect.](https://zeroeyes.com/industry/)
    * [ZeroEyes was founded to protect children from the growing threat of mass shootings nationwide at elementary, middle, and high schools — plus colleges and universities. Our AI-powered, human-verified solution can spot guns on all your campus security cameras 24/7/365.](https://zeroeyes.com/education-security/)
    * [Mass shootings and hate crimes in places of worship and non-profit institutions have increased over the last two decades… and we’re on a mission to stop them. Our best-in-class gun detection solution can help protect your congregation and staff from armed attackers.](https://zeroeyes.com/non-profit-security/)
    * [Founded by a team of military veterans and elite technologists, ZeroEyes helps secure government facilities across America and Canada. Our software is the only one of its kind to hold a SAFETY Act Designation, which means the U.S. Department of Homeland Security has high confidence in our technology’s ability to detect guns.](https://zeroeyes.com/government-security/)
    * [Since 2006, over 75% of workplace mass shootings have occurred at commercial businesses. ZeroEyes holds the U.S. Department of Homeland Security’s SAFETY Act Designation as an effective measure against active shooter situations — protecting your customers and employees and limiting your business’s liability.](https://zeroeyes.com/commercial-security/)
    * [Active shooter threats come from the outside. Keeping guns out of your buildings is vital to combating mass shootings inside. ZeroEyes integrates with your current security cameras to detect visible guns in parking lots, streets, parks and public spaces — even in crowded areas. Make your exterior cameras “smarter” with outdoor AI gun detection and 24/7/365 monitoring.](https://zeroeyes.com/outdoor-security/)
    * [ZeroEyes covers your interiors 24/7/365. We help you to identify critical points to monitor inside your buildings to protect against active shooter threats. Our gun detection solution provides exact shooter location details — granting first responders and security teams more time to lead people to evacuation points and safe zones.](https://zeroeyes.com/indoor-security/)
    * [If you have fewer than 15 digital security cameras, you can still use ZeroEyes through ZEOne. Take a look here.](https://zeroeyes.com/zeroeyes-self-serve-gun-detection/)

    * [Our list of certifications, accreditations and integrations ensure our A.I. gun detection technology works for you 24/7/365 to alert first responders of active shooter threats in as fast as 3–5 seconds.](https://zeroeyes.com/certifications-designations/)
    * [Take an in-depth look at our proprietary technology that sets us apart from the rest—keeping people and places safer from gun violence.](https://zeroeyes.com/technology/)

    * [Proprietary gun violence research, news, incident reports, statistics, and more.](https://zeroeyes.com/mass-shooting-and-gun-violence-research-center/)
    * [At an average cost of less than a few cups of coffee per student, employee or customer per year, ZeroEyes is more affordable than you might think…](https://zeroeyes.com/pricing/)
    * [The latest in school, business, talks about various topics revolving around the ZeroEyes DeepZero AI Gun Detection. Read more about preventing mass shootings.](https://zeroeyes.com/zeroeyes-blog/)
    * [Learn how ZeroEyes’ Strategy team provides data and education for federal, state, and local policymakers about top-of-mind public safety topics.](https://zeroeyes.com/policymakers/)
    * [Frequently asked questions about ZeroEyes and how our AI gun detection system can prevent active shooter and mass shooting incidents.](https://zeroeyes.com/faqs/)
    * [What’s behind the school shootings epidemic and how can we take action? Browse here for American school shooting statistics, data trends, and expert insights.](https://zeroeyes.com/statistics/)
    * [Watch ZeroEyes overviews, media coverage, client testimonials, and more about our AI-powered, human-verified gun detection solution.](https://zeroeyes.com/video-gallery/)

[

](https://zeroeyes.com/)

a

    * [Our team, our mission, and how we can help prevent your people and property from mass shootings and gun violence.](https://zeroeyes.com/about-us/)
    * [ZeroEyes is making headlines. See what people are saying about our AI gun detection technology and the difference it’s making.](https://zeroeyes.com/press/)
    * [See our current partners, view different types of partnerships, and learn how to become a partner and join our mission to end mass shootings.](https://zeroeyes.com/partners-inquiry/)
    * [If you’re seeking purpose-driven work where you’ll make a difference every day, you might be a good fit for our team. Here’s how to apply.](https://zeroeyes.com/careers-portal/)
    * [We actively utilize the DoD-SkillBridge program for transitioning active-duty personnel to the civilian workforce. Find out more now.](https://zeroeyes.com/zeroeyes-skillbridge-program/)
    * [ZeroEyes’ proprietary gun detection technology is an added layer of security, but our human, U.S. military-trained monitoring is what sets us apart from others. Check out our ZeroEyes Operations Centers (ZOC), where we verify threats before triggering real-time alerts and safety protocols.](https://zeroeyes.com/zeroeyes-operations-center/)
    * [We partner with innovative leaders driven to help protect the schools, businesses and communities they serve. Get in touch with us here.](https://zeroeyes.com/contact-us/)

    * [Education, commercial, government, places of worship, non-profit…the list goes on. Learn more about the industries we proudly serve and protect.](https://zeroeyes.com/industry/)
    * [ZeroEyes was founded to protect children from the growing threat of mass shootings nationwide at elementary, middle, and high schools — plus colleges and universities. Our AI-powered, human-verified solution can spot guns on all your campus security cameras 24/7/365.](https://zeroeyes.com/education-security/)
    * [Mass shootings and hate crimes in places of worship and non-profit institutions have increased over the last two decades… and we’re on a mission to stop them. Our best-in-class gun detection solution can help protect your congregation and staff from armed attackers.](https://zeroeyes.com/non-profit-security/)
    * [Founded by a team of military veterans and elite technologists, ZeroEyes helps secure government facilities across America and Canada. Our software is the only one of its kind to hold a SAFETY Act Designation, which means the U.S. Department of Homeland Security has high confidence in our technology’s ability to detect guns.](https://zeroeyes.com/government-security/)
    * [Since 2006, over 75% of workplace mass shootings have occurred at commercial businesses. ZeroEyes holds the U.S. Department of Homeland Security’s SAFETY Act Designation as an effective measure against active shooter situations — protecting your customers and employees and limiting your business’s liability.](https://zeroeyes.com/commercial-security/)
    * [Active shooter threats come from the outside. Keeping guns out of your buildings is vital to combating mass shootings inside. ZeroEyes integrates with your current security cameras to detect visible guns in parking lots, streets, parks and public spaces — even in crowded areas. Make your exterior cameras “smarter” with outdoor AI gun detection and 24/7/365 monitoring.](https://zeroeyes.com/outdoor-security/)
    * [ZeroEyes covers your interiors 24/7/365. We help you to identify critical points to monitor inside your buildings to protect against active shooter threats. Our gun detection solution provides exact shooter location details — granting first responders and security teams more time to lead people to evacuation points and safe zones.](https://zeroeyes.com/indoor-security/)
    * [If you have fewer than 15 digital security cameras, you can still use ZeroEyes through ZEOne. Take a look here.](https://zeroeyes.com/zeroeyes-self-serve-gun-detection/)

    * [Our list of certifications, accreditations and integrations ensure our A.I. gun detection technology works for you 24/7/365 to alert first responders of active shooter threats in as fast as 3–5 seconds.](https://zeroeyes.com/certifications-designations/)
    * [Take an in-depth look at our proprietary technology that sets us apart from the rest—keeping people and places safer from gun violence.](https://zeroeyes.com/technology/)

    * [Proprietary gun violence research, news, incident reports, statistics, and more.](https://zeroeyes.com/mass-shooting-and-gun-violence-research-center/)
    * [At an average cost of less than a few cups of coffee per student, employee or customer per year, ZeroEyes is more affordable than you might think…](https://zeroeyes.com/pricing/)
    * [The latest in school, business, talks about various topics revolving around the ZeroEyes DeepZero AI Gun Detection. Read more about preventing mass shootings.](https://zeroeyes.com/zeroeyes-blog/)
    * [Learn how ZeroEyes’ Strategy team provides data and education for federal, state, and local policymakers about top-of-mind public safety topics.](https://zeroeyes.com/policymakers/)
    * [Frequently asked questions about ZeroEyes and how our AI gun detection system can prevent active shooter and mass shooting incidents.](https://zeroeyes.com/faqs/)
    * [What’s behind the school shootings epidemic and how can we take action? Browse here for American school shooting statistics, data trends, and expert insights.](https://zeroeyes.com/statistics/)
    * [Watch ZeroEyes overviews, media coverage, client testimonials, and more about our AI-powered, human-verified gun detection solution.](https://zeroeyes.com/video-gallery/)

ZeroEyes™
=========

PRIVACY POLICY

Last updated \[March 2023\]

### INTRODUCTION

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. We will alert you about any changes by updating the “Last Updated” date of this Privacy Policy. Any changes or modifications will be effective immediately upon posting the updated Privacy Policy on the Site, and you waive the right to receive specific notice of each such change or modification.

You are encouraged to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed of updates. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, will be subject to, and will be deemed to have accepted the changes in any revised Privacy Policy by your continued use of the Site after the date such revised Privacy Policy is posted.

### COLLECTION OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may collect information about you in a variety of ways. The information we may collect on the Site includes:

#### Personal Data

Personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address, and telephone number, that you voluntarily give to us when you register and login with the Site. You are under no obligation to provide us with personal information of any kind, however your refusal to do so may prevent you from using certain features of the Site.

#### Derivative Data

Information our servers automatically collect when you access the Site, such as your IP address, your browser type, your operating system, your access times, and the pages you have viewed directly before and after accessing the Site.

### MOBILE APPLICATION INFORMATION

If you connect using our mobile application:

* _Geo-Location Information._ We may request access or permission to and track location-based information from your mobile device, either continuously or while you are using our mobile application, to provide location-based services. If you wish to change our access or permissions, you may do so in your device’s settings.
* _Mobile Device Access._ We may request access or permission to certain features from your mobile device, including your mobile device’s bluetooth, camera, contacts, microphone, sensors and other features. If you wish to change our access or permissions, you may do so in your device’s settings.
* _Mobile Device Data._ We may collect device information (such as your mobile device ID, model and manufacturer), operating system, version information and IP address.
* _Push Notifications._ We may request to send you push notifications regarding your account or the Application. If you wish to opt-out from receiving these typeS of communications, you may turn them off in your device’s settings.

### USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

* Having accurate information about you permits us to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience. Specifically, we may use information collected about you via the Site or our mobile application to:
* Assist law enforcement and respond to subpoena.
* Compile anonymous statistical data and analysis for use internally.
* Create and manage your account.
* Email you regarding your account or order.
* Enable user-to-user communications.
* Fulfill and manage purchases, orders, payments, and other transactions related to the Site.
* Increase the efficiency and operation of the Site and our mobile application.
* Monitor and analyze usage and trends to improve your experience with the Site and our mobile application.
* Notify you of updates to the Site and our mobile applications.
* Offer new products, services, mobile applications, and/or recommendations to you.
* Perform other business activities as needed.
* Prevent fraudulent transactions, monitor against theft, and protect against criminal activity.
* Request feedback and contact you about your use of the Site and our mobile application.
* Resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems.
* Respond to product and customer service requests.

### DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may share information we have collected about you in certain situations. Your information may be disclosed as follows:

### BY LAW OR TO PROTECT RIGHTS

If we believe the release of information about you is necessary to respond to legal process, to investigate or remedy potential violations of our policies, or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others, we may share your information as permitted or required by any applicable law, rule, or regulation. This includes exchanging information with other entities for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### THIRD-PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS

We may share your information with third parties that perform services for us or on our behalf, including payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service, and marketing assistance. Information gathered in SMS campaigns will not be shared with Third Parties or Affiliates for their own Marketing Purposes.

### TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

We may use cookies, tracking pixels, and other tracking technologies on the Site and our mobile application to help customize the Site and our mobile application and improve your experience. Most browsers are set to accept cookies by default. You can remove or reject cookies, but be aware that such action could affect the availability and functionality of the Site or our mobile application.

### SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION

We use administrative, technical, and physical security measures to help protect your personal information. While we have taken reasonable steps to secure the personal information you provide to us, please be aware that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse. Any information disclosed online is vulnerable to interception and misuse by unauthorized parties. Therefore, we cannot guarantee complete security if you provide personal information.

### POLICY FOR CHILDREN

We do not knowingly solicit information from or market to children under the age of 13. If you become aware of any data we have collected from children under age 13, please contact us using the contact information provided below.

### OPTIONS REGARDING YOUR INFORMATION

#### Account Information

You may at any time review or change the information in your account or terminate your account by:

* Logging into your account settings and updating your account
* Contacting us using the contact information provided below

Upon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, some information may be retained in our files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Use and/or comply with legal requirements.

#### Emails and Communications

If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails, or other communications from us, you may opt-out by:

* Noting your preferences at the time you register your account with the Site or our mobile application
* Logging into your account settings and updating your preferences.
* Contacting us using the contact information provided below

If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails, or other communications from third parties, you are responsible for contacting the third party directly.

### CONTACT US

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: [Info@zeroeyes.com](mailto:Info@zeroeyes.com)

\[ZeroEyes, Inc.\] (“we” or “us” or “our”) respects the privacy of our users (“user” or “you”). This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you visit our website (www.zeroeyes.com), including any of our other media forms, media channel, mobile website, or mobile application related or connected thereto (collectively, the “Site”). Please read this privacy policy carefully. If you do not agree with the terms of this privacy policy, please do not access the site.

[

](https://zeroeyes.com/)

solutions for...
----------------

about
-----

Technology
----------

Resources
---------

Contact Us
----------

follow us
---------

©ZeroEyes Inc. All Rights Reserved 2023 – Conshohocken, PA [Privacy Policy](https://zeroeyes.com/privacy-policy/)    [Terms and Conditions](https://zeroeyes.com/terms-conditions/)    [Patents](https://zeroeyes.com/zeroeyes-patents/)
